Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Audio Recordings 6140 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Audio Recordings
1968- 1999
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
National Union of Hospital and Nursing Home Employees (NUHHCE)
Local 1199 Drug amd Hospital Union
6140 AV
5.44 cubic feet
5.4 linear ft.
Audiovisual materials.
5817058
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, March 22, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 23, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6085 G: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project "Frederick Douglass and His Time" Posters 6084 G: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Women of Hope Poster Sets 6089 G: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Posters 6069: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Additional Files 6140: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project 6140 P: Local 1199 Moe Foner Photographs 5929 P: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Photographs 5929: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Records 6169 AV: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Audio-Visual Materials 6169: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Files 6169 MB: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Memorabilia 6169 P: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Photographs 5929 AV: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Audio-Visual Materials 5929 MB: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Memorabilia
Collective bargaining -- Hospitals; Davis, Leon; Davis, Ossie; Felshin, Nina; Foner, Moe, 1915-; King, Coretta Scott, 1927-2006; King, Martin Luther, 1929-1968; McCray, Melvin; Turner, Doris; Bread and Roses Cultural Project; National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees
5817058
- Save Our Union Song, 1986; 1 (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents
  1/1986
- 1199 B and R Task Force, 1 (Box 2)
- The Turnergate Tapes: an interview with David White, 1 (Box 3)
- Moe Foner Interviewed by Melvin McCray 6/12/1999, 1 (Box 4)
  Media Genesis Productions 3 Agate Court, Brooklyn, New York, 11213
- TAKE CARE - Performance (1989), 1 (Box 5)
- TAKE CARE - 2/17/1980, 1981; 1 (Box 6)
  Images 9/8/1981
- Workers Culture Conferences -- 11/19/1982, 1 (Box 7)
  The Waiter's Work
- TAKE CARE --- 5/26/1982, 1 (Box 8)
- 1199: Leon Davis - 1959 or 1962, 1 (Box 9)
  Davis to Drugstore Members; You have to pay; Documentary on Beth-El Hospital Strike; Commercials Supporting Strike
- 1199: Leon Davis, 1962; Davis on WWRL -- 1957, 1 (Box 10)
- 1199: M.L. King to 1199, Cont.; Coretta King 1970; M.L. King Short Speech, 1 (Box 11)
- Dr. King and 1199 -- King Speech, 1 (Box 12)
- The Outlook for collective Bargaining in Hospital Industry in New York, 1968; 1 (Box 13)
  Debate between Norman Metzger and Leon Davis 9-20- 1968
- Moe Foner in Sweden 1980, 1 (Box 14)
- WNYC Radio, 1 (Box 15)
  Leon Davis --
- Disarming images, 1984; 1 (Box 16)
  Nina Felshin -- aired on WGVC -- 9/11/1984
- Health PAC Awards Dinner, 1985; 1 (Box 17)
  Moe Foner -- 5/16/1985
- 1199 Convention -- Philadelphia, 1 (Box 18)
  Excerpts from TAKE CARE with Ossie Davis, S. Philips, Gregg Hunter
- Moe Foner -- Health DAC Awards Dinner -- 5/6/1985, 1 (Box 19)
- Doris Turner -- Campaign Spots, 1 (Box 20)
- Save Our Union -- Campaign Spots, 1 (Box 21)
- TAKE CARE LIJ Strike -- 1981, 1 (Box 22)
- WNYC - Moe Foner - Phone interview -- TAKE CARE III, 1 (Box 23)
- TAKE CARE 1991, 1 (Box 24)
- TAKE CARE 5/1/1989, 1 (Box 25)
  Moe, Dennis, Shaw.
- TAKE CARE -- NPR -- 1989 ATC, 1 (Box 26)
- Perspectives - 9/6/1981 -- Special assignment, 1 (Box 27)
  WGEK of 9/7/1981; Interview of Moe Foner; Labor Day Fair
- 1199 Impressions -- Moe Foner, 1 (Box 28)
- Leon Davis Memorial 10/5/1992, 1 (Box 29)
- Ossie and Ruby -- 3/26/1987, 1 (Box 30)
  Tribute 1199; Avery Fisher
- None of the above, 1 (Box 31)
- WBAI Tape - Rise gonna rise - Earl Dotter Exhibit, 1 (Box 32)
- NPR -- 1199, 1 (Box 33)
- Pope Spot on NPR -- 1/19/1984, 1 (Box 34)
- Glen interview O/C, 1 (Box 35)
- Birth of 1199: The Drug Store Years, 1 (Box 36)
- 40th Anniversary -- 1199, 1 (Box 37)
- Hospitals and 1199, 1 (Box 38)
- Worker's Culture: Heartland Labor Forum, 1 (Box 39)
- Elliott Godoff Memorial, 1 (Box 40)
- Moe Foner - Interview for Nat'l Lawyers Guild (1990), 1 (Box 41)
- Folk Music Almanac with Dave Sears, 1 (Box 42)
- Leon Davis Memorial -- 10/5/1992, 1 (Box 43)
- Ossie Davis (1984), 1 (Box 44)
- Save our union spots 1986, 1 (Box 45)
- The Turnergate Tapes: an interview with David White, 1 (Box 46)
- TAKE CARE ATC, 1 (Box 47)
- TAKE CARE ATC (2/17/1980), 1981; 1 (Box 48)
  Images of Labor ME (9/8/1981); Images of Labor ATC (8/17/1981)
- Interview - Moe Foner (3/24/1982, 1 (Box 49)